<?xml version="1.0"?>

<config_bld>

<comment>
This file was produced by the following command:

/home/larsonej/titancam/src/models/atm/cam/bld/configure -spmd -nosmp -dyn fv -res 10x15 -nadv 47 -nnadv 9 -nlev 61 -pcols 4

This is a configuration file for building CAM.  It is the file format
produced by the configure script to store a build configuration.  It
may also be read by the configure script (via setting the -defaults
option) to provide a default build configuration.

This file may be edited by hand to quickly customize a configuration.  If
hand editing is done it should be recognized that XML parser used to read
this file is not able to check the file for valid syntax.  Also, the
current parser places some restrictions on the normally valid XML syntax:
1. Attribute values must be enclosed in DOUBLE QUOTED STRINGS!!!
</comment>

<comment>
cam_bld    CAM build directory, contains .o and .mod files
cam_exedir Directory where CAM executable will be created
cam_root   Root directory of CAM distribution
esmf_bld   Build directory for ESMF, only needed if ESMF lib will be built
esmf_root  Root directory of ESMF distribution, only needed if ESMF lib will be built
usr_src    User source directories to prepend to the filepath.  Multiple directories
           are specified as a comma separated list with no embedded white space.
</comment>

<directories
cam_bld="/home/larsonej/titancam/build"
cam_exedir="/home/larsonej/titancam/build"
cam_root="/home/larsonej/titancam/src"
esmf_bld="/home/larsonej/titancam/build/esmf"
esmf_root="/home/larsonej/titancam/src/models/utils/esmf"
usr_src=""
/>

<comment>
dyn    Dynamics package: eul, sld, or fv
phys   Physics package: cam1 or waccm
chem   Chemistry package: [waccm_mozart | waccm_ghg]
lnd    Land model: clm2
ocn    Use SST data or slab ocean model: dom or som
sice   Sea ice package: csim4
pergro Use modifications that allow perturbation growth testing
           0 => no, 1 => yes
</comment>

<packages
dyn="fv"
phys="cam1"
chem=""
lnd="clm2"
ocn="dom"
sice="csim4"
pergro="0"
/>

<comment>
res     Horizontal grid resolution.  Spectral dycores use Gaussian grids are specified
        by nlat x nlon.  The finite volume dycore uses an equally spaced grid that includes
        pole points and is specified as lat_cell_size x lon_cell_size in degrees.
nlon    Number of longitude grid points
nlat    Number of latitude grid points
nlev    Number of vertical levels
nadv    Number of advected constituents
nnadv   Number of non-advected constituents
trm     Maximum Fourier wavenumber
trn     Highest degree of the Legendre polynomials for m=0
trk     Highest degree of the associated Legendre polynomials
pcols   Maximum number of columns in a chunk
</comment>

<resolution
res="10x15"
nlon="24"
nlat="19"
nlev="61"
nadv="47"
nnadv="9"
trm="1"
trn="1"
trk="1"
pcols="4"
/>

<comment>
cam_exe    Name of CAM executable
cppdefs    User specified CPP defines to append to Makefile defaults.
cc         User specified C compiler overrides Makefile default.
cflags     User specified C compiler options to append to Makefile defaults.
fc         User specified Fortran compiler overrides Makefile default.
debug      Switch to enable debugging options for Fortran compiler.
fflags     User specified Fortran compiler flags to append to Makefile defaults.
fopt       User specified Fortran optimization flags to override Makefile defaults.
ldflags    User specified ld options to append to Makefile defaults.
spmd       Switch to enable or disable building SPMD version of CAM.
smp        Switch to enable or disable building SMP version of CAM.
nc_inc     Directory containing NetCDF include files.
nc_lib     Directory containing NetCDF library.
nc_mod     Directory containing NetCDF module files.
nested_omp Switch for nested OpenMP
mpi_inc    Directory containing MPI include files.
mpi_lib    Directory containing MPI library.
mpi_lib_name Name of MPI library.
target_os  OS for which CAM is being built.
</comment>

<makefile
cam_exe="cam"
cppdefs=""
cc="mpicc"
cflags=""
fc="mpif90"
debug="0"
fflags=""
fopt=""
ldflags=""
spmd="1"
smp="0"
nc_inc="/curc/tools/free/redhat_5_x86_64/netcdf-4.1.3_ict-3.2.2.013_hdf-4.2.6_hdf5-1.8.7/include"
nc_lib="/curc/tools/free/redhat_5_x86_64/netcdf-4.1.3_ict-3.2.2.013_hdf-4.2.6_hdf5-1.8.7/lib"
nc_mod="/curc/tools/free/redhat_5_x86_64/netcdf-4.1.3_ict-3.2.2.013_hdf-4.2.6_hdf5-1.8.7/include"
nested_omp="0"
mpi_inc="/curc/tools/free/redhat_5_x86_64/openmpi-1.4.3_ict-3.2.2.013_torque-2.5.8_ib/include"
mpi_lib="/curc/tools/free/redhat_5_x86_64/openmpi-1.4.3_ict-3.2.2.013_torque-2.5.8_ib/lib"
mpi_lib_name="mpi"
target_os="linux"
/>

</config_bld>
